She told me it was your idea
to send this to me,
and I couldn't thank you enough.
Melissa is very lucky
to have a father like you.
Thank you so much!
Thank you, thank you!
- It's the best.
- Congratulations, ma'am!
[HAZEL] Thank you so much!
[BILLY] In a way,
I should actually thank you.
If you hadn't stolen LoveFeast,
I wouldn't have thought
of something much better.
Which one of us is the bigger thief?
Why don't you just tell the truth,
so I can understand
where your anger is coming from?
[BILLY] I'm sure she just
came here to spy on us.
Hearts Island will be
our next biggest project.
Twenty single women…
[BILLY, JORDAN]
This summer!
Pebblng's newest offering?
We'll choose 20 women searchers,
and we will bring them
to a romantic island
which we'll call Hearts Island.
[LINDSAY] Why is this one
a carbon copy of that?
It's called exactly the same!
Hearts Island!
It's a reality TV show
in the US that flopped.
Get out of my office.
And get out of my company!
I should've listened to Billy.
Billy?
Billy this, Billy that! It's always Billy!
You deserve each other!
[PHONE CHIMING]
- [CONFETTI POPS]
- [SHRIEKS]
- Surprise!
- Wow! A surprise for me!
- Yes, yes!
- Thank you! Oh, thank you!
- Congratulations!
Wow! You actually went all-out!
How sweet! Thank you!
And, of course,
congratulations to all of us.
You stayed.
You fought for us.
For LoveList.
So I promise,
we'll keep making this family stronger.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOCTOR]
Mr. Toledo is cleared for discharge.
He may now be transferred
into your custody.
Okay, Doc.
Guys, it's only been three days
since Happily Ever After,
and memberships are up,
ads are performing.
Investor interest is pouring in!
- Yeah!
- Yay!
Speaking of investors, it's official.
The investors Bea stole from us
pulled out of Pebblng.
In fact, they're asking to set
a meeting with us!
And even business owners
who are not in our original list
are interested in partnering with us!
- Wild!
- Nice!
We have so much to celebrate.
- [BILLY, THEN EVERYONE] Cheers!
- [JORDAN] Cheers to that!
We should celebrate it
along with Jordan's birthday tomorrow.
[TONI] Double celebration!
Your and Billy's birthdays are
only a day apart, right?
Come on, guys! It's just like old times.
It's a double celebration!
- Yeah! Let's go!
- Guys, no.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- [CHARM] Hm?
I already have birthday plans.
- Aww, that sucks.
- [JORDAN] But thank you.
- You're the best.
- [CHARM] What a bummer.
But thank you. You guys are
the best. Thank you.
- Oh my, oh my!
- What a killjoy.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sir.
Huh?
'Bi?
These are your things.
I'll wait for you outside.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EXHALES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
- [CALOY GRUNTS SOFTLY]
- [HANDCUFFS RATTLING]
What is this?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What is it this time?
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[SHARP STAB]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [COP GROANING]
- Stop it!
- [METAL TRAY CLANKS]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [BODY THUDS]
[SNICKERS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GROANING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEA] Hurry up!
I knew you couldn't stay away from me.
We have a lot of work to do.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[TRAFFIC NOISE]
'Bi, thank you.
I'll make it up to you.
From now on, I'll do all the work.
You don't have to do anything because…
- [CALOY EXHALES]
- [GUN CLICKS]
Hey, where did you get that?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I got it from the cops.
You never learn, do you, huh, Caloy?
You can't use that.
Why not?
This will be useful. It still has bullets.
Come on, let's use it.
I want to fire it so bad.
I just said that you can't.
Are you out of your mind?
Chill out.
- What I want…
- [CALOY SIGHS]
is just to give that freaking Billy
a fright.
She's an animal.
She wanted me behind bars.
What an animal.
But I don't think it would hurt
to give her a proper scare.
What do you think?
Hmm?
You want to scare her, babe?
I'll take care of it.
[GROANS]
I said you can't use the gun.
Don't call me babe.
- [BIRDS CHIRPING]
- [MENACING MUSIC FADES]
[CROWD SINGING, CLAPPING]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, happy birthday ♪
- ♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- ♪ Happy birthday to me ♪
Make a wish, son.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[BLOWS]
- Yay! [CLAPS]
- [JUDE CHUCKLES]
[JUDE, JADE CLAPPING]
What's your wish, my dear grandson?
My wish is
long life
for you, Grandpa.
I wish to be with you for a long time.
Oh! But it's your birthday.
Your wish should be for yourself.
You've always put me first. [CHUCKLES]
Don't worry about it, Grandpa.
I have another wish.
Hmm?
Happiness for
the people I care about most.
[MUSIC TURNS BRIGHT]
Isn't it your birthday too?
It's tomorrow, Grandpa.
[JUDE CHUCKLES]
- Come on, blow your candle.
- The three of us should do it.
- Together. Let's go, let's go.
- Okay.
One, two, three.
[ALL BLOW]
Yay!
- [CROWD CHEERS, APPLAUDS]
- Happy birthday!
Okay, time to eat!
Let's eat.
- There's more food there.
- Grandpa!
Time to eat.
- [JORDAN] Enjoy all the food.
- Thank you.
You can eat anything you want today!
- Thanks, dude.
- And later, he can have a slice of cake.
- I asked permission.
- Eat to your heart's content.
Remember. Make some space, okay?
- Cake. Cake.
- Just one slice.
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
You again?!
I told you not to come back!
- Calm down. Grandpa, relax.
- Grandpa, it's okay.
Calm down. It's not him.
- Nurse, please.
- [NURSE] Let's go.
Grandpa.
[JORDAN] Just calm down.
[BILLY] Go ahead and eat, Grandpa.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
I thought I already made myself clear
to your manager.
We asked that that male nurse
stay away from Grandpa Jude.
But according to our manager,
that's just impossible, sir.
- He's on duty and just doing his job.
- [SIGHS]
And what about your job to keep him safe?
Last week, he slipped in the bathroom.
All right, sir. I'll let our manager know.
- Excuse me.
- That works best. Thank you.
Dude.
[SIGHS]
I'm sorry.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Happy birthday!
I'm sorry, dude.
Today was supposed to be fun.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Come on, you don't need to apologize.
It's partly their fault too.
I get it.
This is Grandpa Jude we're talking about.
He's the only family I have left.
I don't think I can handle
losing another loved one.
It'd break me, dude.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[ALL SINGING, CLAPPING]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, happy birthday ♪
- To me!
- [BILLY] Yeah!
- Thank you, thank you.
- [BILLY, FRIENDS] Make a wish!
[BLAIRE] Aww!
[CHEERING, CLAPPING]
Thank you, thank you.
[BILLY GIGGLES]
After what happened earlier,
I thought we needed a redo.
It's still your birthday.
So, happy birthday!
- Thank you.
- Happy birthday!
This was supposed to be just for you.
Oh, since when?
Ever since we were kids, we've always
celebrated our birthdays together.
So it can't be just about me.
Okay, guys. It's almost midnight.
So let's start the countdown!
- That's right.
- Billy, it's almost your day!
- My birthday! Okay!
- Come on, guys! Let's do it!
- Let's do the countdown!
- It's your moment, girl!
- [ALL] Five, four, three!
- [BILLY] Here we go!
- Two, one…
- This is it!
[JORDAN] Not this one.
- Happy birthday!
Oh!
[ALL SINGING, CLAPPING]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, happy birthday ♪
- To me!
- [LAUGHTER, APPLAUSE]
[JORDAN] To you!
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
- Thank you! Thank you, guys!
- [WHOOPING, CLAPPING]
- Happy birthday!
Let's drink!
- Thank you!
[MUSIC FADES, ENDS]
- Ms. Val?
- [VALERIE GULPS]
Can you still handle it? Because…
it's starting to look less
like fun drinking.
[EXHALES LOUDLY]
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
Uh, yeah.
It's… for moving on.
Moving on? [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Yeah, well… [SIGHS]
Kevin and I broke up.
And I guess we really can't
fake sparks, huh?
Yeah. [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Agreed.
Um…
I agree with you, Ms. Val.
If you're meant to be together,
then you will be. But if not…
I guess it's just not meant to happen.
You're so sweet! Thank you!
[VALERIE GIGGLES]
Twinny.
Are you okay?
Have some food.
Would you like a slice of cake?
- Come on.
- No, no, I'm good. [CHUCKLES]
Thank you.
Okay.
- Robbie, my love!
- Hmm?
- This is for you.
- For me?
If it's meant for you,
then you'll have it. Right?
Mm-hmm.
So tell us, bro.
When is your wedding taking place?
We don't have an exact date yet.
Also, we're avoiding too much pressure.
- We're still saving up.
- Mmm.
But if I were a rich man like you,
we'd marry anytime.
- Right, my love?
- You're silly.
Anytime, you say?
He hasn't even proposed yet.
To this day?
Babe.
We'll get there, okay?
Let me guess.
Soon.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- [CHARM] Always soon.
Wait a minute. Excuse me.
Uh, hello, Ma?
Mm-hmm. Yes, yes.
[RALPH] No.
- We're working on it.
- Your competition is tough.
- [SOFT THWACK]
- Hey!
No, it's fine.
It's true.
Here.
This is your birthday gift.
[BILLY] Hmm.
Wow! You're so sweet.
Open it.
No way.
- It's this? You finished it?
- Mm-hmm.
[BILLY] Okay. Okay.
I'll hold your hand in the madness
Run to me if they cast you aside
And if you've lost all drive
I'll be your solace
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
You're making me cry.
[FAKE SOBS]
This is beautiful.
- It's beautiful!
- Really? You like it?
Super.
Best birthday gift ever.
- Happy birthday, dude.
- [BILLY] Thank you.
Well, there you have it!
Did you say best birthday gift ever?
C'mon, boss. Play it for us!
- [CHEERING]
- [BILLY] I'd love that!
- It's just my birthday, no big deal.
- [ROBBIE] Yeah, she's right.
What?
- [TONI] Go, Jordan!
- It's just us! C'mon!
- [YANI] Jordan!
- Indulge me just this once!
[JORDAN] Your day will come, Robbie.
[CHEERING]
- [ROBBIE] Yo! Wait!
- [CLEARS THROAT]
- I'll turn off the lights.
- [TONI] Perfect!
- You don't have to do that.
- [MARJ] Wow!
- [TONI] It needs to be bright.
- [CHEERING] Perfect!
- [BLAIRE] Here we go!
- Okay, okay.
I wrote this as Billy's birthday gift,
but it's inspired by all of you, so.
- This is Sandal.
- [CHEERING] Wow!
- [BLAIRE] How touching!
- [TONI] Here we go.
♪ When you come home ♪
♪ Weighed down and broken ♪
♪ I can tell ♪
♪ By the words unspoken ♪
♪ So come here by my side ♪
♪ Let's leave the rest
Of the world aside ♪
♪ I'll hold your hand in the madness ♪
♪ Run to me if they cast you aside ♪
♪ And if you've lost all drive ♪
♪ I'll be your solace ♪
♪ Just lean on me ♪
♪ Let's just dance
To the beat of our hearts ♪
♪ Just lean on me ♪
♪ When you're crying and don't know why ♪
[ENRICO] I'll never get tired of asking
for your forgiveness, Billy.
I understand why you can't
forgive me right away.
I should've been the one
you could lean on.
But I wasn't there for you.
Either of you.
I just hope you'll give me another chance
to show you how deeply sorry I am,
and how much I love you all.
Happy birthday, my Billy.
I'm very proud of you.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[JORDAN SINGING]
♪ Just lean on me ♪
♪ Let's leave the rest
Of the world aside ♪
♪ With all its baggage ♪
♪ Whatever happens ♪
♪ Lean on me ♪
♪ Just lean on me ♪
- [CHEERING]
- Okay.
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
- Thank you.
- [FRIENDS] That was great!
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm on my way to Billy's.
Be careful, okay?
You're still wanted.
- [LOUD THUD]
- [GROANS]
Caloy escaped!
What?!
- [LINE RINGS]
- C'mon, dude. C'mon!
- Give up already!
- [SCREAMS] Help! Let me go!
[ENGINE REVS]
- Stop it!
- Help!
- [LOUD THUD]
- [GRUNTS]
She fought back, so I beat her up.
I slammed her head against the wall.
Why did you hurt her?
He hurt Billy?
Serves her right!
If one of us gets caught,
we'll all get dragged into this.
She's already ruined
every plan you had for us.
That's why what Caloy did
was the right thing.